现在  我们应该能够找出最
Now, we should be able to figure out the most
适合我们的应用程序使用的URL  基于我们
appropriate URL that our app should use. Based on the
之前看到的用户体验的线框图  你注意到我们
UX wireframes that we saw earlier, you noticed that we'll
需要一个星期的数据  为了便于这个测试和
want one week's worth of data. For this quiz and for
我稍后将要展示给你们的示例代码的进行
the example code that I'll be showing you later,
我们将使用Mountain View的邮政编码
we're going to be using the postal code for Mountain View which is
也即94043  无论如何  你应该使用你自己的位置
94043. By all means, you should use your own location
可以指定邮政编码
either specifying the postal code,
城市名称或纬度经度坐标
city name or the latitude, longitude
接下来  我们希望
coordinates. Next we want their
服务器返回的数据的格式是JSON格式
format from the server to be in JSON format,
并且我们希望使用公制度量标准  但是我们的界面将
and we want the units to be reported in metric. But our UI will
能够根据用户的设置来显示
be able to display Celsius or Fahrenheit
摄氏温度或者华氏温度  我们将
based on user preferences, and we'll just
自己完成转换  在下面的框中
do the conversion ourself. Enter the URL
输入满足这些需求的URL
that fulfills these requirements in the box below,